PETER:
Valentine's Day:
a day of love,
right in the middle
of Black History Month.
There are a thousand hearts
in Quahog,
a thousand stories.
Some people don't have
any stories.
Others got two.
Anyway, here's a song your
girlfriend probably likes.
♪ I got a feeling
♪ That tonight's gonna be
a good night ♪
♪ That tonight's
gonna be a good night ♪
I'm afraid I have
some terrible news:
(gasps)
I have dinner reservations
and no one to go with.
♪ Tonight's the night
♪ Let's live it up
♪ I got my money
Hi, I'll be
your wife's nurse.
Would you excuse me
a second?
Okay, I'm back.
♪ Here we come,
here we go ♪
♪ We gotta rock
♪ I know that
we'll have a ball ♪
♪ If we get down and go out
♪ And just lose it all
♪ I feel stressed out,
I wanna let it go ♪
♪ Let's go way out, spaced out
♪ Losing all control
♪ Fill up my cup
♪ Mazel tov
♪ Look at her dancing
♪ Just take it
♪ Off.
Peter, are you ready
for your Valentine's gift?
No, but I'm ready for therapy.
Peter, you awake?
It's a beautiful day.
Um, yeah, I'm just glad
I didn't die
from the weird
sleep-breathing thing I have.
(screaming)
You know, Peter, since
it's Valentine's Day
I was thinking
let's do something
we've never
done before.
Release the virus?
No, I was thinking we could
spend the whole day in bed.
Oh, that's a great idea.
Permission to begin a day of
epic lovemaking, sexy lady.
Permission
granted, sir.
PETER: And if I need help,
I'll just fantasize
about that Victorian stripper.
Yeah, you slut.
Doth the magistrate know
what you're doing tonight?
Good.
Now, undo the top six buttons
of your 100-button shoes.
Wow, Meg,
you look nice.
You got a date?
Yeah, I totally hit it
off with this great guy
in the Internet, and we're
finally going to meet.
Okay, remember to ask
questions about him.
Seem interested.
Listen. Giggle.
Swallow.
(doorbell rings)
Oh, my God,
that's him.
Toby?
Meg?
Hi. Wow, you look just
like your picture.
You don't look
anything like yours.
Yeah, that's a candid
from a summer job I had.
Well, you're much
prettier in person.
Shall we go?
Yeah, sure.
Don't wait up, boys.
I like him.
Really? He seems
kind of lame.
But, I guess
every girl
has her own version
of Prince Charming.
I'm in love with Paul.
I'm in love
with John.
You know what?
I'm in love
with Ringo.
What?
Um, I said...
I don't-I don't know
what I said.
Sounded like you said you
were in love with Ringo.
Um, I don't...
I don't think so.
Pretty sure you said
"I'm in love with Ringo."
Here I am.
Are Paul and John
out there?
Nope, just Ringo.
Oh, you're still here?
Yeah, after
a wonderful night
I-I thought we could
get some breakfast.
(laughing): Clearly, you're not
familiar with how this works.
See, you're supposed
to be already gone.
There's no breakfast.
Here, let me help you
to the door.
You're a jerk,
Glenn Quagmire.
One of these days, you're
going to get what you deserve.
You better put
something warm on.
You got an icicle
forming down there.
Dumb broad left her
electric tampon warmer.
(screaming)
What the hell?
That's weird.
Why do I look like a chick
in that mirror?
(screaming)
Ah, what's wrong with you,
Holder-Downer 5000?
That's just for women.
Hold it together, Quagmire.
You probably just had
one too many drinks last night.
(siren blaring)
Son of a bitch.
Ah, hey, Joe.
God, I thought
I was in trouble for a minute.
Hey, toots, you know
why I pulled you over?
You were going too
sexy in a 35 zone.
I'll need to see
your driver's license.
What?
Joe, what the hell's
wrong with you?
It's me, Quagmire.
JOE:
Glenda Vajmire.
Well, how would you
like to spend four hours
desperately trying to
give me a muscular soldier?
What the hell,
you weirdo?
(laughing)
I'm just having fun.
In fact, as I say to all
the ladies, giggity-giggity.
You don't say that.
I say that.
You're a bad person.
Hey, Stewie,
what are you doing?
Well, Brian, in honor
of Valentine's Day
I thought why not
go back in time
to that summer of love
in the '60s
that everyone's always
talking about.
Oh, cool.
Hey, you think you might be
able to get me some acid?
I'll get you rolled-up
newspaper on the snout
is what I'll get you.
Very. Bad. Dog.
Well, here we are, Rupert:
Quahog's summer of love.
♪
Ball, please.
Hello.
Oh, this must be yours.
Thanks.
My God, she's incredible.
Rupert, I must bring her
back to the present
and raise her to be my wife.
Oh, God, I bet that diaper
is soaking wet.
I can't let her get away.
Oh, hi.
Oh, hey, um, I just
came to say, um...
you know, in a couple of years
something's going to come along
called Sesame Street.
And I know the name
makes it sounds Asian,
but it's not, and it's
going to blow your mind.
Oh, the hell with it.
The real reason I ran
over here is because
I wanted to do this.
There's my little Lois.
What?
Lois?!
Come on, honey.
Hop in Daddy's car.
You can crawl around
on the floor
while I drink, smoke,
and drive us home.
(hyperventilating)
(gagging)
Oh, my God, Stewie,
what happened?
None of your (bleep)
business what happened.
Geez, you kiss your mother
with that mouth?
Do you like Coldplay?
Uh, am I a dull
white guy?
Yes, I like Coldplay.
God, Toby, I can't believe
how much we have in common.
It's like we were meant
to find each other.
I know.
To us.
Meg, if you were
any more beautiful,
that'd be neat.
So, what should be do next...
(screaming)
Oh, my God!
Toby, what happened?
Oh, I just harvested
your kidney.
(gasps) Look at the
size of this scar.
Sorry. It's my first day
on this job.
Well, where did
you work before?
Circuit City.
So, I haven't worked
in, like, two years.
Toby, I can't believe
you took my kidney.
You bastard!
Sorry, Meg.
Black market organs
are big money
and I promised my bosses
a fresh kidney.
No hard feelings.
Wait!
You also made
a promise to me.
You promised we'd spend
Valentine's Day together.
The whole day.
And I'm not letting you
break that promise.
Well, I guess a deal's a deal.
Okay.
By the way, did you know
you had a tiny conjoined twin
attached to your hip?
Is it worth anything?
It is to me.
I've been using it
as a bookmark.
Peter, what's all this?
Oh, Quagmire loaned me this book
called the Kama Sutra.
It's Indian.
And who has better sex
than people who don't
use toilet paper?
I don't know, Peter.
That doesn't sound very sexy.
What are you
talking about?
Bombay is sperm city.
Slumdog Millionaire?
More like
Scumdog Put-it-there.
Peter, these candles are
getting wax all over the floor.
That's okay. Isn't
Consuela coming today?
No, she spends Valentine's Day
with her husband.
Wait, but she's sneaking
out of the U.S.
This is Arizona.
You can shoot a Mexican
for using a water fountain.
(dress rips)
Oh, I fix later.
(sirens blaring)
Happy Valentine's
Day, Juan.
And to you, mi amor.
One minute, I
freshen up first.
Okay.
CONSUELA:
SГ­, sГ­, sГ­... oh, yeah.
Hi.
Oh, hey, um, I think I might
have the wrong address.
I'm looking for
Mr. Herbert's house.
No, you're at
the right house.
I'm his grandniece,
Sandy.
Wow, my name
is Chris, too.
Oh, hey, there, Chris,
happy Valentine's Day.
Hope cupid brings you
a saggy old bag of treats.
Hey, Mr. Herbert, I'm just here
to collect for the newspaper.
Here you go.
Oh, hang now, Chris.
Your fly's up again.
Thanks, Mr. Herbert.
He's so hot.
(sighing):
I'd love to talk to him,
but I just don't know
what I would say.
Oh, I know all
the things to say.
Maybe I can
help you out.
You'd do that for me?
Sure.
Right after my
favorite show.
Coming up next:
To Catch a Predator
Who's Proud of Being a Predator.
Good evening, sir.
I'm Chris Hansen
with Dateline.
Do you know the boy you were
coming here to meet tonight
is only 13 years old?
No, I drove
900 (bleep) miles
for a 14-year-old.
So what seems
to be the trouble?
Dr. Hartman,
something's wrong with me!
Everyone's treating me
like I'm a broad!
I-I don't know
what's going on!
I recognize that
hysterical tone of voice.
Sounds like someone's
having their monthly.
All right, sweetie,
let me just spit on my hand,
and we'll get started.
Ah! Get away from me,
you creep!
(gasps)
My God!
There was nothing wrong
with my mirror!
Everyone sees me as a woman!
Oh, no!
This is the universe giving me
what I deserve
for being such a pig
all the time!
From now on,
I'm gonna do things differently.
Men are jerks!
Let's swear off of them
and find comfort in each other!
Com here, you guys!
(squeals)
So, what's with you?
No Valentine's Day plans?
(scoffs) No.
I've had it
with Valentine's Day.
I'm sick of all of it.
Okay, I'm putting on
my friend hat.
What's the matter?
Let me in.
I don't know.
It's just...
How come it's so hard
to meet the right woman?
I think maybe it's just time
for me to give up.
Come on, Brian.
You can't give up.
Everything could
change in a moment.
That's what happened with
the Kennedy assassination.
I'm sorry, gentlemen.
Despite our best efforts,
the Texas School Book Depository
Awareness Council has failed
in its mission to generate
public awareness
of the Texas School
Book Depository.
So at the end of the day,
we'll be shutting
down operations
and laying
everyone off.
Sir, I think you're
gonna want to see this!
♪ Let's fall in love
♪ Why shouldn't we fall
in love? ♪
♪ Our hearts are made of it
♪ Let's take a chance
♪ Why be afraid of it?
♪ Let's close our eyes
♪ And make our own paradise
♪ Little we know of it
♪ Still, we can try
to make a go of it ♪
♪ Let's fall in love.
Oh, Brian,
there you are.
Look, I've been
thinking about
your situation
with women,
and I believe
I've come up with a way
to get to the source
of the problem. Follow me.
What's going on?
Oh, my God.
Stewie, what the hell?!
These are all
my ex-girlfriends!
Well, I thought they could
provide some insights
that might improve
your love life.
Ladies, as you may have guessed,
you are here
because you have all dated
this great guy.
Yet, somehow, things
didn't work out.
My objective is
to figure out why.
I don't know.
The word "self-absorbed"
comes to mind.
And pretentious.
Definitely pretentious.
And he's got a big eggo.
Okay, we seem
to have a theme going here.
Oh, come on!
You're all just mad
because I didn't
wanna be with you!
(masculine voice): I think Brian's
a wonderful man.
He's just having
a difficult time
coming to terms
with his own sexuality.
Shut up, Ida.
She's my favorite.
He's insecure.
And a blowhard.
And he's got a tiny penis!
(all laughing)
Yeah, that was pretty clear
by the survey.
Okay, now who wants
more wine?
This is great.
We should do this
every Saturday.
No, no, we're not gonna
do this every Saturday!
What's wrong?
We're just being honest.
Oh, oh, you want honest?!
You're an old bag.
You're blind.
Your vomit tastes weird.
You don't even know
why you're here.
You chose to be
on The Hills.
You still have
bits of penis left,
and you can never get wet.
(whines)
And you, you're more
of a woman
than anyone else
in this room!
Get him!
Oh, honey, I'm so excited
to finally meet your girlfriend.
Here she comes now.
Yoo-hoo, baby!
Oh, no!
ANNOUNCER: We now return to Tom & Jerry:
The Final Episode.
So, that's it?
That's it.
This is so much easier.
I don't know why
I didn't do this years ago.
What do you want me
to do with the body?
(scoffs) I don't care.
Throw it in the garbage.
Do you want any
of his oversized mallets?
I will take a mallet.
(phone rings)
Ah, I gotta take this.
Who's calling?
My ex-girlfriend.
She calls me drunk
every Valentine's Day.
Hey, Samantha.
Yeah, yeah, I'm sorry.
I still love Lois.
Oh, come on. You would have
been a great mom.
(whispering): She had cervical cancer
five years ago.
She's basically a boob
on a leg at this point.
Well, that's something.
You're in a book club?
Those are tough
to get into.
What? Well,
I didn't even know
the Fine Young Cannibals
were still together.
Eight-city tour?
Well, I don't know
if I can make eight,
but I can certainly do six.
What about Lois?
She's totally out
of the picture.
We've done everything
but sign the papers.
Samantha, Samantha,
I will see you in Binghamton.
And now I want you to go
and take a picture of yourself
because it will be
your last day alone.
Geez, what's not clear
about "Get lost"?
By the way, my attendance
at home is gonna be spotty
over the next few weeks.
And, well, prize pumpkin
from the county fair,
that's why I'm naming you
my Chief of Police.
Mayor West, there's
something you need to see!
My God! My wife is
seeing another mayor!
I'm sorry, sir.
Don't be. Because
I'm going to win her back.
I trust you'll take care
of things here in my absence.
Officer down!
I hereby declare
this public park
and future homosexual
meeting spot... open!
Unhand that woman,
you bastard!
(gasps) Adam!
Well, well, well, if it isn't
Mayor "Guns For Toys" West.
The chair recognizes
your face!
En garde!
Is the park open?
Not yet!
You call that kissing a baby?!
That's how you kiss a baby.
I hereby declare this
Stabby Eye Day!
(screams)
Oh, Adam, I'm so sorry!
Carol, I love you
and I can't live
without you.
Please, never let this happen
again.
I won't, Adam.
You're the only mayor for me.
Hey-ey, Carol.
I almost didn't recognize you
without my special sauce
all over your face.
Is somebody out there?
Chris, it's me!
Uncle Herbert's
grandniece, Sandy!
Oh, hi, Sandy. What's up?
(hushed):
What do I say?
You say,
"Chris, I wanted
to come see you
because, well..."
Chris, I wanted to come
see you because, well...
I'm kind of a
lonely old man.
Really?
Now, I know I'm not much
to look at,
and ever since I got banned
from the arcade,
I don't know what I'm doing.
But if you're up for it,
I'd like to spend some time
with you.
Okay. Sure, Sandy!
I'll come right down!
Thanks, Uncle Herbert.
I don't know how
I could ever repay you.
Well, there
is one thing.
(both laughing)
Also, if I gave you
a sandwich,
do you think you could
get Chris to fart on it?
Well, guess
I better be going.
I gotta get this heart
to Madonna.
Oh, my God! Madonna needs
a heart transplant?
No, she just doesn't want
other people
to have them
for some reason.
But before I go... Here.
For me?
My kidney!
I wanted you to have it.
Oh, Toby, I love it!
Thank you.
This has been the best
Valentine's Day ever.
Oh, Peter, it was fun
spending the day
in bed with you.
It sure was, Lois.
Happy Valentine's Day.
Hey, Lois,
remember our wedding?
Yeah, I sure do.
Remember the dance?
Of course I do, Peter.
Who was that
half-Persian chick
who was dancing
with your cousin?
I think her name
was Flora.
Yeah... yeah.
Okay, all right,
I'm ready! I'm ready!
What?
Shut up for ten minutes
and pretend we're in the back
behind the speakers.
(moaning)
This wedding sucks, huh?
♪
♪ L is for the way
you look at me ♪
♪ O is for the only one I see
♪ V is very, very
extraordinary ♪
♪ E is even more than anyone
that you adore can ♪
♪ Love is all
that I can give to you ♪
♪ Love is more than just
a game for two ♪
♪ Two in love can make it
♪ Take my heart
and please don't break it... ♪
(screaming)
Thank you for watching «Family Guy» on
www.FOX-fan.ru